<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hdds on 2nd Grade Magazine</title>
    <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hdds on 2nd Grade Magazine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:15:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastfins</title>
      <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/fastfins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:15:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/fastfins/</guid>
      <description>Fastfins are not afraid of eels. Normally, all dragons are afraid of eels but not fastfins. However, Summer is a fastfin and she is afraid of eels. Why? When she was little, she was playing with her friends in an ocean. Her friends swam away and when she turned to follow, there was an eel and it bit her. And that is why Summer is afraid of eels.
(When my dad was little, a rooster attacked him and then for a long time, he was afraid of any birds that came near him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Furies</title>
      <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/fire-furies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/fire-furies/</guid>
      <description>When two or more Fire Furies shoot the biggest fireball they can at the same time into the air and the fireballs crash together, it makes a big explosion that looks like fireworks.
For example, in Furious Fun (Season 1, Episode 12), Aggro, Laburn, and Cinda make a huge firework.
Go back to Hedvika&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Diary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Dragons</title>
      <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/golden-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/golden-dragons/</guid>
      <description>Golden Dragons are legendary. They lay an egg only once every 100 years. Golden Dragons can shoot streams of golden glitter. The glitter is hard to get off once it sticks and you definitely don&amp;rsquo;t want to get it in your eyes.
Gemma appears in the special Hunt for the Golden Dragon.
Go back to Hedvika&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Diary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relentless Razorwings</title>
      <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/relentless-razorwings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/relentless-razorwings/</guid>
      <description>Relentless Razorwings are known for having awesome eye sight. They can find basically anything, even a needle in a haystack.
(For example, in Secrets of the Songwing, Cutter finds Aggro on an island far away.)
Go back to Hedvika&amp;rsquo;s Dragon Diary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiftwings</title>
      <link>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/swiftwings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2gmag.github.io/hdd/swiftwings/</guid>
      <description>Swiftwings are the fastest dragons on the planet. They are so fast that if they came to Earth, they would fly faster than a peregrine falcon. They would be faster than a mole on a motorbike. They are great at flying tricks. They have three powerblasts and when they are old enough, they can have one megablast.
For example, in Grumblegard Part 2 (Season 1, Episode 14), Winger defeats the Slinkwings with a megablast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>